http://www.cpadfw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Whitley Penn
About Us Leadership Locations PressIndustries Employee Benefit Plans Energy Estate Planning Family Office & Owned Businesses Financial Institutions Healthcare Manufacturing, Wholesale & Retail Nonprofit Private Equity & Alternative Investments Professional Services Public Sector Real Estate & Construction Restaurant & Entertainment Transportation & Logistics Technology Veterinary MedicineServices Audit
Private Companies Public Companies
Consulting
Mineral & Asset Management Strategic Consulting Oil & Gas Consulting Outsourced Accounting Solutions – WP Edge
Forensic, Litigation & Valuation
Business Interruption Claims Business Valuation Commercial Litigation Family Law Fraud & Forensics Intellectual Property Personal Injury, Wrongful Death & Lost Wage Claims
Risk Advisory
Custody Rule Examinations Cybersecurity Enterprise Risk Management Internal Audit IT Consulting Process Consulting Sarbanes-Oxley (SOX) SOC Reporting
Tax
Federal Income Tax Financial Statement Tax Provision (ASC 740) International Tax IRS Controversy State & Local Taxation
Transaction Advisory
13 Week Cash Flow Modeling Business Modeling Buy & Sell-Side Quality of Earnings Post-Transaction
Wealth Management – WPWealthEventsResources Covid -19 Resources Brochures Insights Podcast WhitepapersCareers Current Openings Internship Opportunities
Make A PaymentContact UsClient Login
About Us Leadership Locations PressIndustries Employee Benefit Plans Energy Estate Planning Family Office & Owned Businesses Financial Institutions Healthcare Manufacturing, Wholesale & Retail Nonprofit Private Equity & Alternative Investments Professional Services Public Sector Real Estate & Construction Restaurant & Entertainment Transportation & Logistics Technology Veterinary MedicineServices Audit
Private Companies Public Companies
Consulting
Mineral & Asset Management Strategic Consulting Oil & Gas Consulting Outsourced Accounting Solutions – WP Edge
Forensic, Litigation & Valuation
Business Interruption Claims Business Valuation Commercial Litigation Family Law Fraud & Forensics Intellectual Property Personal Injury, Wrongful Death & Lost Wage Claims
Risk Advisory
Custody Rule Examinations Cybersecurity Enterprise Risk Management Internal Audit IT Consulting Process Consulting Sarbanes-Oxley (SOX) SOC Reporting
Tax
Federal Income Tax Financial Statement Tax Provision (ASC 740) International Tax IRS Controversy State & Local Taxation
Transaction Advisory
13 Week Cash Flow Modeling Business Modeling Buy & Sell-Side Quality of Earnings Post-Transaction
Wealth Management – WPWealthEventsResources Covid -19 Resources Brochures Insights Podcast WhitepapersCareers Current Openings Internship Opportunities
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Notice Required by LawYour privacy is very important to us. CPAs, like all providers of personal financial services, are required by law to inform clients of their policies regarding privacy of client information. CPAs have been, and continue to be, bound by professional standards of confidentiality that are even more stringent than those required by law. This notice is to provide you with an understanding of the type of information we collect as well as how we use and dispose of that information.Types of Nonpublic Personal Information We CollectWe collect non-public personal information about you that is provided to us by you or obtained by us with your authorization. Information provided to us via the Contact Us form located on our website is not used for any reason other than the one stated by the person submitting the form.Parties to Whom We Disclose InformationWe do not disclose any non-public personal information of current and former clients obtained in the course of our practice except as required or permitted by law. Permitted disclosures include, providing information to our employees, and in limited situations, to unrelated third parties who need that information to assist us in providing services to you. In all such situations, we stress the confidential nature of the information being provided. Whitley Penn LLP will only disclose information to unrelated third parties under a contractual agreement that prohibits them from disclosing or using the information for any purpose other than the specific purpose for which it was disclosed. Unless otherwise noted, we may distribute information to you via facsimile or e-mail to the numbers and addresses provided by you.Protecting the Confidentiality and Security of Current and Former Client InformationWe retain records relating to the professional services we provide so that we are better able to assist you with your professional needs and, in some cases, to comply with professional guidelines. In order to guard your non-public personal information, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with professional standards.Disposing of Confidential Current and Former Client InformationWe engage the services of a document destruction company for the shredding of hard copies of confidential documents and information. Additionally, we delete electronic data files that have been retained in accordance with our record retention policy.Your privacy, our professional ethics, and the ability to provide you with quality financial services are very important to us.Whitley Penn LLP
Nexia InternationalWhitley Penn is a member firm of the “Nexia International” network. Nexia International is a leading worldwide network of independent accounting and consulting firms, providing a comprehensive portfolio of audit, accountancy, tax and advisory services.“Nexia International” also refers to the trading name of Nexia International Limited, a company registered in the Isle of Man, which operates the Nexia International network. Company registration number: 53513C. Registered office: 1st floor, Sixty Circular Road, Douglas, Isle of Man, IM1 1SA.Nexia International Limited does not deliver services in its own name or otherwise. Nexia International Limited and the member firms of the Nexia International network (including those members which trade under a name which includes the word NEXIA) are not part of a worldwide partnership. Nexia International Limited does not accept any responsibility for the commission of any act, or omission to act by, or the liabilities of, any of its members. Each member firm within the Nexia International network is a separate legal entity.Nexia International Limited does not accept liability for any loss arising from any action taken, or omission, on the basis of the content on this website or any documentation and external links provided.The trade marks NEXIA INTERNATIONAL, NEXIA and the NEXIA logo are owned by Nexia International Limited and used under licence.References to Nexia or Nexia International are to Nexia International Limited or to the “Nexia International” network of firms, as the context may dictate.Description for this block. Use this space for describing your block. Any text will do. Description for this block. You can use this space for describing your block.
Whitley Penn is a member of Nexia International, a leading, global network of independent accounting and consulting firms. Please see the “Member firm disclaimer” for further details.
About Us | Leadership | Industries| Services | Events | Resources | Careers | Privacy Policy | Locations |
Download Adobe Reader | Nexia International | Make A Payment
Copyright © 2020 Whitley Penn
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. RejectAcceptPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
